在代码里  我们将要在PlaceholderFragment这个类的OnCreateView()里初始化
In our code, we're going to initialize the adapter within the placeholder
我们的Adapter适配器  那是我们希望在ListView视图里呈现给
fragment on create view method. Because that's where we want the list view to
用户的数据  我们使用一个数组适配器  我们用四个参数来初始化
be populated with data. We're using a array adapter, and we can initialize it
Context  列表条目布局的id
with four parameters. A context, the ID of a list item layout,
TextView组件的id  以及原始数据列表
the ID of a text view within that list item layout, as well as a list of data.
我们来一个一个讲讲
We'll go through each of these parameters one by one now. First, for
Context  它描述的是一个应用程序环境的信息  即上下文
context. It contained global information about the App environment.
通过它我们可以获取应用程序的资源和类
It allows us to access system services and resources, as well as the application
也包括一些应用级别操作  这里我们使用由Fragments填充的Activity作为Context
specific resources that we've defined. We use the fragments containing activity
所以  这个参数我们调用getActivity()这个方法填充
as the context. So, we're going to call getActivity for our parameter here.
然后这个Adapter适配器需要知道每个条目的布局信息
Since the adapter needs to know the layout for each list item, and
需要通过我们已经在XML文件中定义过id的布局来调用
needs some reference to the XML layouts that we've defined. The r.java class is
R.java 这个文件是自动生成用来统一定义我们所有资源文件的东东
a generated file that creates human readable identifiers for our resources. For
列表项目的布局信息  我们可以通过代码中调用 R.layout.list_item_forecast  来得到
the list item layout, we refer to it in code as r.layout.list_item_forecast.
这是我们早些时候创建的XML文件里的东西
This was the name of the XML file that we created earlier. Next,
下一步  适配器需要将天气情况的数据显示在
the array adapter needs to know how to take the weather forecast string and
一个TextView组件里  所以通过我们之前给TextView创建的那个ID
set that to be displayed in a text view. So you pass in the ID of the text view
就可以调用它了  虽然这两个资源ID看起来很像
that we defined earlier, in the list item layout. Even though these two resource
一个是以R.layout开始的  另一个是以R.id开始的
IDs look similar, one starts with R.layout while the other starts with R.id.
R.layout意味着要去布局文件中找相关内容  而R.id则是从XML布局文件中
R.layout refers to a layout file, while an ID refers to a specific [UNKNOWN]
精确的定位到你曾为其设定为某个ID的元素  最后  我们提供一周的天气预报
element with the matching ID attribute. And lastly, we pass in a week forecast,
通过之前定义的那个包含天气信息的数组
which is the array list of forecast data that we defined earlier.
现在就可以初始化你的Adapter啦  做完的话请在这个复选框打勾
Now go ahead and initialize your adapter. Check this box when you're done.